{
    "subject": "Frederick_Augustus_II_of_Saxony",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Archduchess_Marie_Caroline_of_Austria",
    "human_readable": "Frederick Augustus II of Saxony is married to Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872057437896729,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage between Frederick Augustus II of Saxony and Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9836195111274719,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Frederick Augustus II of Saxony and Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9745481014251709,
            "question": "Who was Frederick Augustus II of Saxony married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9646115303039551,
            "question": "Who is Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9627353549003601,
            "question": "Who was married to Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.961281955242157,
            "question": "To whom was Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9578860998153687,
            "question": "Identify the wife of Frederick Augustus II of Saxony."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9391364455223083,
            "question": "Was Frederick Augustus II of Saxony married to royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9270012974739075,
            "question": "What is the name of the monarch who was married to Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8081259727478027,
            "question": "What was the name of Archduchess Marie Caroline's husband?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Augustus II of Saxony is married to Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria.",
            "html": "yago_19729_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the monarch who was married to Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria?",
            "html": "yago_19729_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Frederick Augustus II of Saxony married to royalty?",
            "html": "yago_19729_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Identify the wife of Frederick Augustus II of Saxony.",
            "html": "yago_19729_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19729_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Prince Frederick Augustus of Saxony (also known as Frederick Augustus II) was married twice, first to Archduchess Caroline of Austria and then to Princess Marie Anne Leopoldine of Bavaria (not Archduchess Marie Caroline of Austria). Neither marriage had any children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19729/re-ranker-msmarco/86.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19729/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt`, which state that Archduchess Marie Caroline Ferdinanda of Austria married Prince Frederick Augustus of Saxony, who was the King of Saxony."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}